quickmark.com.tw 2019-12-31

# QuickMark QR Code Reader - Barcode Scanner - Privacy Policy

**Updated June 25th, 2014**

## Privacy Policy

This privacy statement ("Privacy Policy") explains how information is collected and utilized by AngleTech, Inc. ("AngleTech" or "we", "us", "our") its subsidiaries and affiliated companies. This Privacy Policy applies to the QuickMark website at www.quickmark.com.tw (the "Site"), the QuickMark application for various platforms (the “App”) and QuickMark's other online or mobile services. If you have any concerns about privacy on the Site/App, please send an email to service@quickmark.com.tw and we will try to address it. 

### What Personal Information Does AngleTech (QuickMark) Collect?

When AngleTech uses the term personal information in this policy, AngleTech is referring to information that specifically identifies an individual (such as an individual's name, address, telephone number or e-mail address), and information about that individual or such individual’s activities or preferences when such information is directly linked to personal information. Personal information does not include aggregate information, which is data we collect about the characteristics and activities of users of the Site, the App, and AngleTech's other online or mobile services, from which any personal information has been removed. This privacy policy in no way limits or restricts our collection of aggregate information or of non-personal information. AngleTech collects the following types of information from its Site, App, and related services: 

AngleTech collects the following types of information from its Site, App, and related services: 

  * **Information That You Provide Us:** We receive and store personal information you choose to enter on our Site/App, or provide us in any other way, such as by telephone or by electronic mail. For example, when you register for our services or purchase products/services at our website, we collect personal information about you. This information may include your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, and mobile device information. We may combine the information that you submit on our Site/App with information about you that we receive from other online and offline sources in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the overall quality of our services. In general, the more information you feel comfortable giving us, the more we can personalize the experience of our products and services to meet your needs. When purchasing products/services from AngleTech, your credit card information is not processed nor retained by AngleTech. 
  * **Information That We Automatically Collect:** We may utilize cookies or other technologies of similar purposes to automatically collect information about visitors to our Site/App. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that reside within your browser to enable our computer systems to recognize your browser and to tell our systems how and when pages within our Site/App are visited, used, and by how many people. These technologies from our Site/App do not collect personal information such as phone numbers, addresses, or contacts. 

We may automatically receive and store certain other types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, our servers might track the type of mobile phone or Web browser you are using, where you travel within the Site/App, the page to which you link from the Site/App, and barcodes you interact with. This type of collective data enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of the Site/App, so we can make the Site and App appealing to as many customers as possible. 

### How Does AngleTech (QuickMark) Use the Personal Information That It Collects?

We use the information we collect to provide our services and to better understand what products and services are of interest to our users. For example, we may utilize your information to: 

  * Operate and improve our Site, App and services
  * Respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service
  * Provide and deliver products and services and send you related information, including but not limited to: confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages
  * Protect the rights or property of AngleTech or our users, and 
  * Communicate with you about promotions, upcoming events, and other news about products and services offered by AngleTech and our partners.
  * Perform analysis of aggregate information. AngleTech may share aggregate information about you with advertisers, publishers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties.

### Does AngleTech (QuickMark) Share the Personal Information That it Collects?

We do not share your personal information except as approved by you or as described below:

  * **Agents and Service Providers:** We may engage other companies and individuals to perform services on our behalf. Example of these services is sending postal mail to you. While these agents and service providers may have access to your personal information in connection with the performance of services for AngleTech, they may not use such information for any purpose other than providing such services to AngleTech.
  * **Protection of AngleTech and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe that release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our user Agreement; or protect the rights, property, or safety of AngleTech, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  * **Corporate Transfers and Financings** AngleTech may share your personal information in connection with any merger, sale of AngleTech assets, or a financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.
  * With your consent, for example, when you agree to our sharing your information with other third parties for their own marketing purposes subject to their separate privacy policies;

### How Secure Is the Personal Information That You Provide to AngleTech (QuickMark)?

AngleTech takes reasonable measures to protect your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information that we receive.

### Changes

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time, at our sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Site so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the "Last Updated" date above.
